Welcome to Airtel Payments Bank's Comprehensive
Health Cover Training Video.
Health risks and
uncertainties are part of life.  It is extremely important to buy a health insurance policy for
yourself and your family due to rising medical costs in the wake of increasing medical emergencies.
Medical emergencies can cause significant financial stress
and disrupt your life.
You can avoid this with good coverage at a very low cost.
Airtel Payments
Bank understands your needs and hence
we are pleased to announce our health insurance plans in partnership with ICICI Lombard
that will provide financial cover to
you and your family during hospitalization.
ICICI Lombard Group Health Shield 360 Now let's take a
look at ICICI Lombard's Group Health Shield 360 product.  You will find all this
covered here.  Hospitalization
expenses, day care treatment surgery, normal
room rent and ICU room rent.
Cover up to 30 days prior to hospitalization.  Cover up to 60 days
post hospitalization, unlimited reset benefit.
No Claim Bonus for various diseases Up to 100% Organ Donor
Expenses Hospitalization
Road Ambulance Charges up to ₹000 Om
Hospitalization Alternative Treatment AYUSH Unlimited
Tele Consultation No Co-payment Sum Assured and
Type of Plan Here you
get multiple options of sum assured.  As you
can see on the screen.
These plans cover hospitalization medical expenses for adults including you and your
spouse and children above 91 days of age.
waiting period.  The initial waiting
period is 30 days.  But you
get cover for accidental claims from day one.   There is a
waiting period of 24 months for slow-growing diseases like cataract, hernia, piles, kidney stones, gall bladder stones etc. and 36 months for pre-
existing diseases like diabetes,
hypertension, asthma etc.
If you make claims there are more than 14,000 network
hospitals where you can avail cashless facility
and you can
also get reimbursement for non-network hospitals.
You can make claims like this.
To initiate a claim, you
can contact your insurer via email or call.
Their contact information is provided on your screen.
You can also file a claim with ICICI Lombard by downloading the IL Tech Care app
and logging in with the mobile number mentioned in your policy
[Music].
Click on the Comprehensive Health Cover icon.  Enter the customer's mobile number.
Tap the check box and then
click the Next button.  Now enter the
verification code sent to the customer's mobile number
and click on proceed.  If the
customer has not received the code then you
can click on the resend button after 60 seconds.  On the next page you have to select the sum assured and
plan type like Khud or Khud Plus
Jeevansathi.  After selecting these details
you will see the plans and premiums as per your customer's requirement.
Click on View All Benefits to see the complete list of benefits covered under the plan.
You can also compare both the plans by clicking on the Compare Both Plans button at the bottom of the page.
To select any plan, click on the Buy Now button shown on the plan card.
You can
also choose the plan by clicking on the Buy Now button on the Benefits card.
After selecting the plan, you will be asked to
confirm the customer's personal information.
After confirming the details you will have to
submit the family details.  Such as
member's name,
date of birth,
gender, health declaration.  You will
also need to confirm the nominee details.  Like
Name of Nominee, Date of Birth of Nominee,
Relationship of Nominee, If Nominee is a Minor then Name
of Minor.
Once you submit the family details
click on Proceed button to view the final premium.  The customer will
receive a verification code on their registered mobile number.  This SMS
contains all the details including health declaration.
On the next page you can confirm details like plan details, sum assured
and member details.
You will need to provide a
health declaration from the primary insured.
Please note that the second declaration is
for auto renewal of policies in the next year by auto debiting the amount from the customer's account.  Please
submit the OTP sent to the customer's registered mobile number.
On clicking Proceed, you will have to provide Retailer
Declaration.
On clicking Proceed you will be redirected to the payment page.
After submitting your MPIN,
you can view the details of the policy being issued.
If the policy has been issued
then the status of issued policy will be shown.
If the policy is awaited then the status of Policy Awaited will be
shown.  Tap the Home button to return to the app's home page.   The
insurer will also send an SMS and email to the customer
within 24 hours with the policy details and policy copy link.
Click here to start certification.
humble
up
brother